let quiz   =[
    {question: "Write the smallest 3-digit number using all digits '9','5','7' only once ?",
option:[
    759,
    576,
    579,
    597,

],
answer:3, 
},

{
    question: "918 X 9814 X _____=0." ,
option:[
    918,
    0,
    1,
    9814,

],
answer : 2, 
},
{
    question: "7780 < 7795 - ___?",
option:[
    40,
    10,
    90,
    50,

],
answer:2, 
},
{question: "What number can be multiplied by 5878 to give the answer 5878?",
option:[
    0,
    2,
    1,
    5878,

],
answer:3, 
},

{
    question: "If today is Monday, then what will be date after tomorrow ?",
option:[
    "Wednesday",
    "Tuseday",
    "Thursday",
    "Friday",

],
answer : 1, 
},
{
    question: "How many hours and minutes are there from quarter past 5 to half past 8?",
option:[
    "2 hrs 30 mins",
    "3 hrs 10 mins",
    "2hrs 15 mins",
    "3 hrs 15 mins",

],
answer:4, 
},
{
    question: "What unit of length would you choose to measure the length of your pen?",
option:[
    "Meter",
    "Centimeter",
    "Kilometer",
    "None of these",

],
answer : 2, 
},
{
    question: "18 kg 657 g is equal to ____grams." ,
option:[
    "18657 g",
    "17757 g",
    "18695 g",
    "18655 g",


],
answer:1, 
},
{
    question: "If one orange weighs 250 grams, then what is the weight of 7 oranges?",
option:[
    "2kg 750g",
    "1kg 250g",
    "1kg 750g",
    "2kg 250g",

],
answer : 3, 
},
{
    question: "85 liter 37 milliliter is equal to _____milliliter.",
option:[
    "8537 ml",
    "85370 ml",
    "8547 ml",
    "85037 ml",

],
answer:4, 
},
{
    question: " There are 45832 men,41985 women and 33859 children in a town. What is the population of the town?",
option:[
    121678,
    98078,
    112678,
    111678,

],
answer : 1, 
},
{
    question: "Which of these factor pairs makes the product 48?",
option:[
    "6 and 6",
    "4 and 8",
    "6 and 8",
    "5 and 8",

],
answer:3, 
},
{
    question: "Which number comes after -4 on a number line ? ",
option:[
    -5,
    -3,
    -2,
    "None of these",

],
answer : 2, 
},
{
    question: "Which is smallest ?",
option:[
    0.3,
    0.5,
    0.4,
    0.8,

],
answer:1, 
},
{
    question: "Which is not equivalent to 1/2 ?",
option:[
    "2/4",
    "4/8",
    "3/6",
    "2/3",

],
answer:4, 
}]